# Ayala Bergman – Full Stack Developer

## 054-8495154 | ayala5154@gmail.com

Experienced developer with 10+ years of experience in the architecture, design, and implementation of large-scale systems with a focus on performance, optimization, and adherence to industry standards.

Proficient in PHP, Node.js, Python, React, and databases such as MySQL and MongoDB. Team player with strong communication skills.

Seeking a challenging position as a Full Stack or Backend Developer to express my abilities and experience and promote the organization.

### **Professional Knowledge**

Backend Development: PHP, Python, Node.js, Rest API, Linux

Frontend Development: React Redux, Next.js, Angular, JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML, CSS

Databases: MySQL, MongoDB, Redis

Cloud Platforms: Azure, AWS

Tools/Technologies: GIT, Docker, Copilot, OOP, Design Pattern

Work Methodologies: Agile, Jira

#### **Experience**

## 2023 - Today | Tigloo | Backend Developer

- Development and deployment of a complex tracking system in the Fintech field, ensuring high performance and compliance with industry standards,
- Writing APIs, crafting complex database queries and implementing optimizations.
- Developing unit tests and utilizing monitoring tools.
- Working with Agile methodology and Git

### 2020 - 2023 | Mipo Technologies | Full Stack Developer

- End-to-end product design and development, including server-side (PHP- YII) and client-side (React, Next.js), CI/CD, and deployment (80% Hands-On, Management of 2-4 Programmers)
- Experience in the architecture of data structures and writing complex queries.
- Working with Agile methodology and Git

## 2018 - 2020 | HealthPro | Backend Developer

- Development and deployment of the CRM system in the field of alternative medicine, including writing Rest API (PHP- Laravel) and complex database queries (MySQL).
- Developing unit tests.
- Working with Agile methodology and Git

#### 2013 - 2017 | Anova Technologies | Full Stack Developer

- End-to-end development of web systems, including server-side (PHP) and client-side (JS, Angular, HTML, CSS, JQuery).
- Development and integrations with third parties, such as credit clearing systems/CRM/mailing and more.
- Leading projects while mentoring additional developers

#### **Education**

2010 - 2012 | College of Management | Software engineering studies on behalf of Mahat

**Languages Hebrew** – native | **English** - good level.